So y'all was mad, rightfully, that the lady who accused Emmett Till of looking at her
and got him murdered in Mississippi, y'all were rightfully angry that she was never called
to justice and in her 80s were calling for her to go to prison and die in prison.
You remember that, right?
You same people, and she's a private citizen.
You same people are completely fine with members of the United States government enacting
a genocide and getting off scot-free.
And I want you to ask yourself why.
Because rightfully, you want reparations from that same government for slavery.
Like you're like, nah, y'all can't get off scot-free for that.
However, I want you to ask yourself why you're okay with Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton not
being held accountable for taking down Libya and assassinating Muammar Gaddafi, all to keep
the American dollar in control of the world.
I want you to ask yourself why you're completely fine and okay with George Bush getting to eat
hard candy with Michelle Obama, even though he actively put forth in motion him and his vice
president, Dick Cheney, for the murder of over a million Iraqis.
I want to ask you why you're okay with Joe Biden and Kamala Harris continuing to live their best
lives.
Why the genocide they propagated and that they pushed completely false information to create
manufactured consent for continues to exist.
It's happening right now.
Why do you think it's acceptable that they get to trot around and not be challenged or questioned?
Why do you think you're not seeing people protesting Donald Trump?
Because it's happening literally every single day.
So either you're bots or you're bullshitting.
By the way, I actually know the answer, but I'm gonna come back with that another time.